ondeck.com 2016-04-17

# Privacy Policy | OnDeck

  * This Privacy Policy has been updated effective June 11, 2015.

This Privacy Policy applies to [www.ondeck.com](https://www.ondeck.com/) (“Website”), which is owned and operated by On Deck Capital, Inc. (“OnDeck,” “Us,” or We”). The Website facilitates our business loan products and related services (collectively “Services”). This Privacy Policy describes how OnDeck collects and uses the personal information you provide (directly or through third parties), or which is automatically generated, when you interact with our website [www.ondeck.com](https://www.ondeck.com/) (“Website”) and our mobile application (“Mobile App”).

This Privacy Policy also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update such information. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means information that personally identifies you, including your contact information, IP address, and loan application information. A large portion of the Personal Information we collect, use, share, and store is sensitive in nature, including your social security number and financial account information (“Sensitive Personal Information”). 

OnDeck has received TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and our 

practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily in this Privacy Policy or otherwise, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. Please click [here](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us) for fax and postal mail information for TRUSTe.

Unfortunately, TRUSTe’s Dispute Resolution process is only available in English. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Website, and does not cover information collected through third party sites or services, or information that may be collected through software downloaded from the Website.

* * *

  * We collect the following information from you:

    * Contact information such as name, business name, email address, mailing address, and phone number;
    * Financial information such as bank statements, credit card statements, your average bank balance, personal and business credit history, payment behavior, bank account information, and tax ID number;
    * Social security number;
    * Unique identifiers such as user name and password, and IP address; and
    * Business information including company size, and business type.

In addition to collecting information via our Website and Mobile App, we may also conduct a site visit to collect information, and obtain information and external data used by lenders to process applications and complete and manage transactions, e.g., from credit reporting agencies and other vendors, as well as from social media. Once you are an OnDeck customer, we may reach out to you for, or otherwise obtain, information if you decide to renew your loan or as otherwise needed to provide the Service. 

* * *

  * We use the information we collect to:

    * Compile, save, use and analyze your Personal Information in both a personally-identifiable form and an aggregated, non-personally identifiable form;
    * Operate, maintain, improve, and provide to you the Service and to conduct our business;
    * Verify your identity and conduct appropriate diligence;
    * Register you as a user and identify you when you sign in to your account;
    * Process your application and determine whether or not your business qualifies for one of our loan products;
    * Process your business loan product account, including deducting automatic payments;
    * Communicate with you to send order confirmations, respond to customer service requests, send marketing communications, and send account update notifications;
    * Post and review your comments on our blog.
    * Conduct research and analyses to better understand our customers; and
    * Produce data analytics and reports containing anonymized summaries of Personal Information and other information that is not Personal Information (such information, “General Information”) that we share with business partners. General Information may include Personal Information that has been aggregated, anonymized and will not identify you.

* * *

    * OnDeck will share your Personal Information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy and as required by law. We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. 

We will provide your Personal Information to our trusted business partners, service providers and subsidiaries and affiliates to provide services to help us with our business activities, such as offering customer service, processing credit checks or secure data storage, and other similar services. These companies are authorized to use your Personal Information only as necessary to provide these types of services to us. In addition, we may share your basic information (name, company name, phone number, email address and requested loan amount) with one of our business partners to market their services to you , provided, however, if you do not want us to share your Personal Information in these circumstances with these business partners, please contact us to opt out by email at [marketing@ondeck.com](mailto:marketing@ondeck.com) or by postal mail at the contact information listed below. In addition, we may also share General Information for the same reasons as we provide Personal Information and for business partners and others to conduct analyses and research and track marketing performance or as otherwise provided in the Tracking Technologies part herein. 

Some of our pages utilize framing or white-labeling techniques to serve content from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our Website. For example, our Careers page utilizes white-labeling techniques. Please be aware that in these instances you are providing your Personal Information to these third parties and not to OnDeck.

We may also disclose your Personal Information:

      * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, including in a bankruptcy proceeding;
      * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a request from a governmental entity;
      * If OnDeck is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or substantially all of its assets or equity, in which case, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information; and
      * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

* * *

    * If your Personal Information changes, or if you no longer desire our Service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, ask to have it removed from a public forum or testimonial on our Website or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at [marketing@ondeck.com](mailto:marketing@ondeck.com) or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 30 days. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as reasonably useful for commercial purposes. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

      * _Opt-Out Policy_

OnDeck and our business partners may contact you to offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails, telephone solicitations or other forms of contact from OnDeck and our trusted business partners by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or by contacting us by email at [marketing@ondeck.com](mailto:marketing@ondeck.com) or by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

* * *

    * Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by OnDeck and our partners (for example, our marketing partners), affiliates, or analytics or service providers, including our live chat, marketing trackers, and survey tool service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the Website, tracking users’ movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for user authentication and analytics. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our Website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our Website may be limited. If you would like to learn more about cookies or how to configure your browser, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

      * _Log Files_

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you and to improve marketing, analytics, and Website functionality. 

      * _Local Storage Objects (Flash/HTML5)_

Our partners use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our Website or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 or Flash to collect and store information. 

Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

      * _Behavioral Advertising/Re-Targeting_

We partner with third parties to display advertising on our Website and manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this Website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertisements. You will continue to receive generic advertisements.

* * *

    * OnDeck takes the security of your information very seriously. Your information is securely sent to OnDeck with 128 bit-encryption over the Transport Layer Security (TLS) protocol. This creates an encrypted connection between your browser and our servers. Thus, when you enter Sensitive Personal Information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information. 

If you allow OnDeck to see your banking information online rather than in paper form, it is on a read-only basis. We do not have access to change, edit, or modify bank account information in any way. OnDeck employees cannot view your banking username and passwords.

* * *

    *       * _Links to 3rd Party Sites_

Our Website includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of OnDeck. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. 

      * _Blog/Forum_

Our Website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. _To request removal of your Personal Information from our blog or community forum, contact us by email at[marketing@ondeck.com](mailto:marketing@ondeck.com) or by postal mail at the contact information listed below_. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your Personal Information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

      * _Testimonials_

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us by email at [marketing@ondeck.com](mailto:marketing@ondeck.com) or by postal mail at the contact information listed below.

      * _Social Media Widgets_

Our Website includes social media features, such as the Facebook “Like” button. These features may collect your IP address, which pages you are visiting on our Website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

      * _Changes To This Policy_

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

* * *

    * If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us by email at [marketing@ondeck.com](mailto:marketing@ondeck.com), or with a letter by postal mail to:

On Deck Capital, Inc.  
ATTN: Marketing  
1400 Broadway. 25th Floor  
New York, NY 10018  
USA   

If you are contacting us to opt-out of marketing communications, you must include your full name and business mailing email addresses and account number. Once we locate your contact information based on the information you provide us, it will be removed from our databases and mailings lists.
